Indiana University Bloomington Professional Council records, 1980-1998 C210
Indiana University Archives
- Membership, 1984-1998
  - Elections, 1986-1996
    - Biographical Sketches, 8 Apr 1986 - 5 Jul 1995 (Box 3)
    - Council Members Election Statements, 8 Apr 1986 - 15 Jul 1996 (Box 3)
    - IUB Professional Staff Council Elections, 7 Mar 1986 - 1995 (Box 3)